This kid?
It has a spirit.
Who's the spirit?
If not hurry to chase
This house will definitely disappear.
So what should I do?
Chanjao,
She said that you ask her to pick up the earrings.
That child is delirious.
But she is not a liar.
Now I have no meaning in this house.
If worshiping each other.
Then bring it up to the worshiping shelf.
It's like coming to the same place.
Thep, Thep, Thep.
Sir,
What are you doing here?
The lady asked for you.
I don't know.
Where have you been?
Go to pay respect to your uncle and aunt.
Can you remember me?
I'm glad to see you again.
Chanjao,
I think I won't see you anymore.
Suddenly, my parents moved here.
Dad said that it is very far from our house.
Yes.
Very far away.
Well...
Are you following me?
You can say that.
But really, I live here.
Otherwise...
I will see you often, right?
Yes,
Mom hires a special teacher.
If I'm older than this, I can go to school.
Why can't you go to school?
Mother said,
I bruise easily and bleed easily.
Black bruise.
Chanjao,
Where are you?
Are you okay?
I'm fine, let's find Chanjao.
Chanjao,
Where are we going?
Go to play.
Hide and Seek.
Thep,
Chanjao would not walk this far.
Do we go back to look at the car?
Chanjao,
Thep,
The blood still doesn't stop flowing.
What do we take to stop the bleeding?
No need.
It's dead
Don't be sad
You tried your best to help.
Should we help bury it?
- Chanjao,
Chanjao,
Ouch!
- Ouch,
- Ploy,
Ploy,
I'm sure your leg is sprained.
I can do it.
I am at the land.
It's just a dense forest.
I heard there are abandoned houses there too.
I think I will walk to see.
As for the price, I still don't know.
Yes, I'll ask the people around here.
Are you ok?
Chanjao.
Ploy,
You hurry to find Chanjao.
Hurry, don't worry.
And you?
It's okay, you hurry to find Chanjao.
Yes,
Chanjao,
Hurry to find Chanjao.
- Chanjao,
I met her lying unconscious over there.
Thank you.
Chanjao,
We just drove the car.
Please follow me.
Yes,
I'll go get the car first.
Chanjao,
Where are you hurt?
What are you looking for?
Elder sister.
She invited me to go for a walk.
Huh?
Sister?
Well...
Uh ...
And the blood on you handkerchief,
Is the blood of that sister?
No,
I try to stop the bleeding.
And why did that sister leave you alone?
Go, let's go.
Should be caused by problems
that our booking system.
I have to apologize.
It's okay.
I'll go see it.
Thank you.
Do you have any problems?
The room that my seniors booked.
Someone has stayed.
Manager,
Uh, I have to apologize.
We will be responsible.
We will contact the hotel room.
For you to rest without charge.
But may be a little far away.
Are you convenient?
I think it's already dark and...
My child is already very tired.
The important thing is that my wife hurts.
Uh...
How about...
Go to stay at my house?
It's just close to here.
And now who is in the room 1101?
Female customers, name...
That woman, she just checked in half an hour ago.
Chat,
Give the key card for the guests. She dropped it and forgot.
Which one?
Well, the guests who walked by you.
Which guest?
No, not funny.
You can go to see the camera.
Your house is very beautiful.
Yes,
When did this house come from?
King Rama VII.
I like this kind of Sino -Portuguese style
building from time to time.
I went to Phuket Penang and Malaka.
Go to see the house looks like this.
What do you call it?
Shino-Portuguese.
Really?
I don't have any knowledge of art or architecture.
In fact, I don't even have knowledge
about this house.
I first came here.
Just a few days before you guys.
And how did you get this house?
It's the inheritance that my father gave me.
Please come in.
Yes,
Let's go to the market.
We will save money to buy a motorcycle.
And then will buy a house.
As big as Luang Decha.
Okay,
Now,
Stacked the bike first.
Hold my waist so that you won't fall.
Is it your house?
Here, Luang Dejadireksorn.
He's my great-grandfather.
And also the person who built this house.
And...
This person is a grandfather.
My great-grandfather was a great merchant who did
so much good that he was awarded a royal title.
I know it because of...
Google.
Really,
I don't know much about my father's ancestors.
My parents broke up.
And I moved to a foreign country since childhood.
Is there anything?
I just wondered.
What a picture was this before?
I think the room should be finished.
You guys go to rest first.
Yes,
Wait a minute.
The lady want to get the item back.
What item?
The clock necklace from Mr. Thep.
Where is it?
Look,
It's broken.
We don't want anyone's stuff.
If you want to take it back, ask nicely.
It's not that we're poor.
Then you can act like
a commoner however you want.
Are you saying I'm a commoner?
What are the fuss?
Lady, asked to get the item back.
Bring it to me.
Oh,
Phorn,
You can take it back.
But...
Nevermind,
I'll accept it.
Is your name Buanga?
I am Mok.
The second wife of the lord.
Your lady is not compassionated me.
I will accept one more thing.
It's better than me having to
endure seeing people being bullied like I was.
If you want to take it and tell your boss,
that's up to you.
Go back.
Oh, I'll let people take the car to deliver.
It's okay.
Please accept my kindness.
I really like that.
But there is nothing to compensate like others.
Why not go home yet?
I'll will go up now.
- Let's go home.
- Yes,
My bedroom is straight over there.
If you are missing anything, you can call me.
Thank you.
Tonight, let's just sleep together.
I'll find a new accommodation tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
The first day I took you to be difficult.
Nevermind.
Busy is also good. I'll not have much time to think.
I'm so glad.
To marry you.
We should go to sleep.
I'll turn off the light.
Good Night.
Thep,
Close the lid, drag, and tilt.
Place,
Turn,
Next, slow down.
Return.
I doubt they'll go outside.
Let's come the next day.
Kem,
Buanga,
I brought the medicine.
It's a foreigner medicine.
There are both topical and oral medications.
The wound will heal faster.
Thank you very much.
But the next day, do not be difficult to arrive here.
Our house is in disrepair.
Not worthy of you,
we cannot welcome you properly.
I am not the rank of anything.
My age is the same as your child.
You can called me Thep.
And most importantly,
I never thought of a deserved.
We all are equal.
You're strange.
If really equal,
Buanga probably did study abroad like you.
Stay in a big house.
Like a palace like you.
This is already different just from birth.
We are really different.
But we are equal.
I am a little knowledge
I don't understand what you say.
You should go back. If the Lord and Lady find out,
they will definitely not be pleased.
Teacher,
What's the matter?
The village headman told us
to terminate our employment.
Then go to hire a group of Phatthalung instead.
Did he told you why?
I don't know.
But as I know,
Village headman is a distant relative
with Lady Duangkae.
Can you tell what happened?
Sorry, it fell last night.
I'll take it to fix.
And will bring it back.
It's okay. I broke it myself.
I'll just keep it like this.
Where have you been?
I'm currently obsessed with this book.
Yesterday, I read half of the book.
Before Uncle Kam returned
What did you talk to him?
Go to see in the kitchen first.
We talked to each other as a relative.
Why?
Did anyone report anything?
Nothing.
But I heard that Uncle Kham
has cancelled the Nora Jiam troupe.
What does it have to do with you?
It has nothing to do with it.
Uncle Kham wants a Nora Yai,
someone who has been ordained and studied,
not just someone who only dances beautiful.
Are you sure that you didn't tease them.
Are you accusing me?
Thep,
I apologize.
Raj want to play with Thep since morning.
Mother said that you plays many western sports.
Please teach me.
Please,
Yes,
The era has changed.
This time, love is above the suitability.
If Thep likes Nora's daughter.
You have to accept it.
She can speak because you're
the daughter of a merchant.
Not much different from that girl.
You must understand.
Very good.
This way.
You're clever. This way.
Brother Thep praised me for
being quick - witted and having very good feet.
Very good.
- Is that mine?
- Yes,
All favorite things.
I know what happened.
But if you argued with your mother,
it's even worse for Buanga.
The lady is strict person, but not vicious.
One day, she'll give up.
If she see that you and Buanga
really love each other.
So what to do?
This good fabric, I don't know where to cut it.
Please return it back to Mr. Thep.
Cut to make merit on this big Buddha day.
Take it.
I told the shop to cut the set already.
That the younger sister named Buanga will be there.
No need to pay.
Like this, I can't accept it.
Don't be.
Thep is very sincere with you.
Don't make him sad.
There is a lot of people.
Unfortunately father can't join us.
Oops,
Lady,
Look at that.
Do you see?
Buanga is actually coming.
And look at it, dress up.
Poor and not modest, I hate it.
- Aunt Porn.
- Oh, what?
We try to make merit.
It made the lady's mood cloudy.
Oh, Lady doesn't think about that, right?
Go.
Right?
You haven't been around for ten years.
Hoping be with you for a long time.
But I had to send him far again.
Yes,
Because if you didn't send Khun Thep far away,
he'll definitely have to return to Buanga.
Sigh!
Sorry to made you shocked.
But what are you doing here?
Oh,
I come to find Thep.
I saw he went out of the room for a long time,
so I walked and came to see.
But I've searched everywhere and still can't find him.
He may go back to the room.
Try again.
But if not found, I'll help.
Yes,
Chanjao,
MChanjao,
Here,
Some things have owners
We should not be busy.
And who is the owner?
Giving time is giving a part of life.
It's a pity that the watch doesn't work anymore.
I really like this place.
It's already feeling so good that I can't tell.
But I think it looks scary.
We just came here yesterday.
Believe me.
Peekaboo.
And why did she curse me?
She hates your ancestors.
Isn't she in my family?
You have to find an answer by yourself.
My friend sent the news that there was
a vacancy at the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
Gradually feel a little more comfortable.
You must hurry to marry Buanga
before going to Bangkok.
Mother would never agree.
If so, you have to escape.
Buanga is my wife.
He must hurt.
Suffer.
Must be screwed like he did to me.